♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
( farting )
♪ GONNA HAVE MYSELF
A TIME ♪
♪ FRIENDLY FACES
EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ HUMBLE FOLKS
WITHOUT TEMPTATION ♪
♪ GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA LEAVE
MY WOE'S BEHIND ♪
♪ AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT ♪
♪ PEOPLE SPOUTING
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" ♪
♪ HEADED ON
UP TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA SEE IF
I CAN'T UNWIND ♪
( mumbling )
♪ SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO YOU ♪
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
DEAR GRANDPA ♪
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO YOU ♪
NOW BLOW OUT
THE CANDLES GRANDPA.
( wheezing )
HOORAY!
HOW'S IT FEEL TO BE
102, PAPS?
SHOOT ME!
MAKE A WISH,
GRANDPA.
I WISH
I WERE DEAD!
THAT'S OUR
SILLY GRANDPA.
I'M NOT BEING SILLY,
KILL ME!
I'D DO IT MYSELF
BUT I'M TOO DAMN OLD!
WHO WANTS ICE CREAM
WITH THEIR CAKE?
( Stan )
I WILL!
IT'S 8:00, MY FAVORITE
TV SHOW IS ON.
THAT SHOW'S FOR BABIES,
IT'S SO STUPID!
CAN I EAT MY CAKE
IN THE LIVING ROOM MOM?
PLEASE, CAN I?
OH, ALRIGHT, BUT TAKE
YOUR GRAMPY WITH YOU.
GODDAMNIT!
LANGUAGE!
Now back to
"Terrance and Phillip".
Hey Terrance,
I think I have to fart.
Wait, before you do,
pull my thumb.
( farting )
( laughing )
( gunshot )
GODDAMNIT!
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO MAKE A DOLLAR, BILLY?
MY NAME'S NOT BILLY,
GRANDPA, IT'S STAN.
DAMNIT BILLY,
DO YOU WANT A DOLLAR?!
SURE.
YOU JUST HAVE TO DO
ONE THING.
I'M NOT GONNA
KILL YOU GRANDPA.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE I'LL
GET IN TROUBLE.
I KILLED MY GRANDPA
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE!
LEAVE ME ALONE
GRANDPA.
( farting )
WHAT HAS AMERICA'S
YOUTH COME TO?!
KIDS WON'T EVEN KILL
THEIR OWN GRANDPARENTS!
Hey Terrance,
now that you farted,
I think I might
fart too.
( farting )
You farted!
( laughing )
KYLE, BUBBY,
WHAT ARE YOU WATCHING?
Hey Phillip, would you
like a flower?
I sure would,
Terrance.
Alrighty then,
here's a tulip.
( farting )
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S HORRIBLE!
DUDE, IT'S
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP".
Take that you,
stupid dick.
WHAT DID
HE SAY?
You're an asshole
Phillip.
WH-WH-WHAT?!
YOUNG MAN,
YOU ARE NOT TO WATCH
THAT SHOW ANYMORE.
IT'S IMMATURE
TOILET HUMOR.
BUT EVERYBODY WATCHES
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP".
OH, REALLY,
IS THAT SO?
Oh, no, Phillip looks like
you're about to fart.
You're exactly
right Terrance.
( farting )
SWEET.
ERIC, DEAR,
I JUST GOT A CALL FROM YOUR
FRIEND KYLE'S MOTHER.
SHE SAID THAT
THIS SHOW IS NAUGHTY
AND MIGHT MAKE YOU
A POTTY-MOUTH.
THAT'S A BUNCH OF CRAP!
KYLE'S MOM IS A DIRTY JEW!
OH, OKAY, HON.
I'M NOT GOING
TO KILL YOU GRANDPA!
INGRATE!
GOOD NIGHT
GRANDPA!
YOU POMPOUS
SON OF A WHORE!
OW, WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT FOR?
THAT'S FOR YOUR
STUPID MOTHER!
SHE MADE ME MISS
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP"
LAST NIGHT.
YEAH WHAT'S
THE BIG IDEA
HAVING YOUR MOM CALL
ALL OUR MOMS LAST NIGHT?
I DIDN'T HAVE HER DO IT,
SHE DID IT ON HER OWN.
WHY DOES THIS HAPPEN
EVERY MONTH?
IT SEEMS LIKE RIGHT ABOUT
THE SAME TIME EVERY MONTH
KYLE'S MOM GETS A HAIR
UP HER ASS ABOUT SOMETHING
AND I ALWAYS END UP
GETTING SCREWED BY IT.
CHILDREN, CHILDREN,
A CERTAIN STUDENT'S MOTHER
CALLED ME LAST NIGHT.
GEE, I WONDER WHO'S MOTHER
THAT COULD'VE BEEN.
SHE INFORMED ME THAT
SOME OF YOU MIGHT BE WATCHING
A NAUGHTY SHOW CALLED
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP".
( all giggling )
WATCHING THAT SHOW
IS BAD, MR. GARRISON.
THAT'S RIGHT,
MR. HAT.
SHOWS LIKE
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP"
ARE WHAT WE CALL
"TOILET HUMOR".
THEY DON'T
EXPAND YOUR MINDS.
YOU SEE CHILDREN,
THESE KINDS OF SHOWS
ARE SENSELESS,
VILE TRASH.
KENNY, WHY ARE YOU
LATE TO CLASS?
OH, OKAY,
KENNY BE SEATED.
NOW AS I WAS SAYING,
THE REASON THE PARENTS
OF SOUTH PARK ARE SO UPSET
IS BECAUSE--
YES KENNY,
WHAT IS IT?
( mumbling )
YOU JUST CAME
FROM THE BATHROOM.
( loud mumbling )
OKAY, OKAY,
GO AHEAD.
AS I WAS SAYING, YOU ALL
SEEM TO ENJOY THE SHOW
EVEN THOUGH IT ISN'T
BASED IN REALITY.
THERE'S MUCH MORE TO LIFE
THAN TWO YOUNG MEN
FARTING ON EACH OTHER.
( loud diarrhea sounds )
AND THROUGHOUT HISTORY
THERE HAVE ALWAYS BEEN SHOWS
THAT HAVE COME AND GONE
THAT HAVE BEEN VERY BAD
AND USUALLY THEY GET TAKEN
RIGHT OFF THE AIR.
YOU SHOULD BE SPENDING YOUR TIME
ENLIGHTENING YOUR MIND
WITH MORE INTELLIGENT
ENTERTAINMENT.
SMELLS LIKE YOU SLAUGHTERED
A COW IN THERE KENNY!
PAY ATTENTION
CHILDREN!
I'M GOING TO JOIN
YOUR PARENTS IN REQUESTING
THAT YOU DON'T WATCH
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP"
ANYMORE EVER.
WHAT?
NOT WATCH IT EVER?
THAT'S RIGHT CHILDREN,
ARE THERE ANY QUESTIONS?
YES STANLY?
IS IT OKAY TO KILL SOMEBODY
IF THEY WANT YOU TO?
WHAT--
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
MY GRANDPA KEEPS ASKING THAT
I KILL HIM ALL THE TIME.
SOMETIMES I WONDER
IF I SHOULD.
I THINK THAT A PERSON HAS
A RIGHT TO DIE IF THEY WANNA.
REALLY?
THERE'S THIS GUY
NAMED JACK LABORKIAN
THAT GOES AND AND MURDERS PEOPLE
THAT ASK HIM TO.
AND HE DOESN'T GET INTO
ANY TROUBLE AT ALL.
WOW!
MAYBE WE CAN GET HIM
TO KILL KYLE'S MOM.
SO IS IT OKAY TO ASSISTANT
SOMEBODY WITH SUICIDE?
STAN...
I'M NOT TOUCHING THAT ONE
WITH A 20 FOOT POLE.
( loud mumbles )
( diarrhea sounds )
I THINK I'M ALREADY
HAVING WITHDRAWAL.
( moaning )
DON'T WORRY, WE CAN ALL
WATCH IT AT MY HOUSE.
MY PARENTS DON'T
GET HOME UNTIL LATE.
BUT WON'T YOUR
GRANDPA BE THERE?
YEAH.
JUST KILL HIM
DUDE.
MAYBE HE'LL GIVE YOU
SOME MONEY.
HELLO THERE
CHILDREN.
HEY CHEF.
HOW'S IT GOING?
BAD.
WHY BAD?
CHEF, IS IT OKAY
TO KILL YOUR GRANDPA?
YOU CAN'T KILL
MY GRANDPA STAN.
HE'S ALREADY
PASSED ON.
NO I MEAN KILL
MY GRANDPA.
NO, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S OKAY.
IN FACT I THINK
THAT'S ILLEGAL.
SEE, I TOLD YOU
DUDE.
WHAT IF THE GRANDPA
WANTS TO DIE
'CAUSE HE'S REALLY OLD AND
HE'S JUST ASKING FOR HELP?
YEAH, LIKE ASSISTED SUICIDE,
WHAT ABOUT THAT?
I DON'T WANNA TOUCH THAT
WITH A 40 FOOT POLE.
WHAT'S THE
BIG DEAL?
WHY WON'T ANYBODY
TALK ABOUT THIS?
AND I MYSELF WAS NOT AWARE
OF THIS HORRIBLE SHOW
UNTIL RECENTLY.
I HAVE A CLIP TO DEMONSTRATE
EXACTLY WHAT I MEAN.
Hey Phillip
guess what?
What?
Fart.
NOW APPARENTLY THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY.
( laughing )
HE FARTED RIGHT ON HIS HEAD.
NOT ALLOWING OUR KIDS
TO WATCH THIS SHOW
IS NOT ENOUGH.
WE NEED TO BOYCOTT
THE ENTIRE NETWORK!
ALL THOSE IN FAVOR!
( loud diarrhea )
I THINK I'VE CAUGHT
A TOUCH OF THE FLU
FROM LITTLE KENNY
THIS MORNING.
I'VE GOT THE GREEN APPLE
SPLATTERS.
( laughing )
HI GRANDPA,
I BROUGHT MY FRIENDS OVER
TO WATCH TV.
BILLY, HELP GRANDPA STICK
THIS FORK IN THE OUTLET!
NO GRANDPA,
I'LL GET IN TROUBLE.
KILL ME
GODDAMNIT!
NO, I CAN'T EVEN
KILL A DEER.
THEN HAVE ONE OF YOUR
LITTLE FRIENDS DO IT.
YOU CAN KILL ME,
CAN'T YOU?
I WOULD NEVER
KILL SOMEBODY.
NOT UNLESS
THEY PISSED ME OFF.
IS THAT A FACT?
WELL LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING, PORKY,
YOUR MOM WAS
OVER HERE EARLIER
AND I HUMPED HER
LIKE A LITTLE BITCH.
WHAT?!
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THEN I DUG UP YOUR
GREAT GRANDMA'S SKELETON
AND HAD MY WAY
WITH HER TOO.
CHOICE PIECE OF ASS
YOUR GREAT GRANDMA.
YOU PIECE OF CRAP,
I'LL KILL YOU!
THAT'S THE
SPIRIT TUBBY!
C'MON, HE'S JUST
TRYING TO GET TO YOU.
DON'T TALK ABOUT
MY MOM LIKE THAT!
WE CAN GO WATCH
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP"
IN THE KITCHEN.
I EVER TELL YOU ABOUT THE TIME
I BOOFED YOUR DAD, FATSO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT SON-OF-A-BITCH!
HERE CARTMAN,
HAVE SOME SNACKY CAKES.
DUDE,
SNACKY CAKES?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO, DUDE.
MY GRANDPA REALLY
WANTS TO DIE.
I'M TELLING YOU
IT'S OKAY.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD ASK
THE LORD FOR GUIDANCE.
HEY, YEAH.
( tv )
And now back to...
on South Park
Public Access.
Believe in me and
ye shall find peace.
First caller you're on
"Jesus and Pals".
( man )
Yeah, is this Jesus?
YES CALLER, YOU NEED TO
TURN YOUR TV DOWN.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE GETTING
THAT WEIRD FEEDBACK.
Oh, sorry.
This is Martin.
Martin from Aspen Park,
yes I know.
How the hell'd
you know that?
MAYBE BECAUSE I'M
THE SON OF GOD, BRAINIAC.
NOW DO YOU
HAVE A QUESTION?
Yeah, I have this cousin
who cheated on the SAT's--
TELL LITTLE GREGORY
THAT CHEATING IS LYING
AND LYING IS WRONG NO MATTER
WHAT THE CIRCUMSTANCE.
Oh.
Okay, thanks
for the advice, Jesus.
NEXT CALLER,
YOU'RE ON THE AIR.
JESUS?
Yes my son.
IS IT OKAY TO KILL SOMEBODY
IF THEY ASK YOU TO
BECAUSE THEY'RE IN
A LOT OF PAIN?
LIKE ASSISTED SUICIDE,
IS THAT OKAY?
MY SON...
YES?
I'M NOT TOUCHING THAT
WITH A 60 FOOT POLE.
NEXT CALLER.
GODDAMNIT!
I HEARD THAT.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH EVERYBODY?
HEY YOU GUYS,
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP" IS ON!
DO YOU THINK WE'LL GET
IN TROUBLE FOR WATCHING IT?
KYLE, DON'T BE
SUCH A BUTT-HOLE.
YEAH, JUST 'CAUSE YOUR MOM
IS A STUPID BITCH
DOESN'T MEAN THE WHOLE WORLD
HAS TO SUFFER.
DON'T CALL MY MOM
A BITCH, CARTMAN!
A BITCH.
YOUR MOM
IS A BITCH.
( tv )
And now back
to "Terrance and Phillip".
Hey Phillip, would you
like to eat some beans?
Oh, yeah,
I love beans!
UH-OH, I BET I KNOW
WHAT'S COMING.
BILLY, WOULD YOU MIND HOLDING
THIS FOR GRANDPA PLEASE?
OKAY
GRANDPA OKAY,
JUST GET OUT OF
THE WAY OF THE TV.
Hey Phillip,
it looks like those beans
might make me fart.
Well don't fart
on me, terrance.
DUDE, HE'S GONNA FART
ON HIS HEAD AGAIN!
( loud mumbling )
HEY YOU'RE GONNA
MISS IT, KENNY!
( farting )
You're such an
asshole Terrance!
That's right
I am!
( exploding diarrhea )
KENNY, YOU'RE GONNA
MISS THE FART!
JESUS, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?!
WE'RE NOT WATCHING
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP",
I SWEAR.
I MEAN CARTMAN
WAS WATCHING IT.
NO, I MEAN
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING
TO GRANDPA?!
TUG A LITTLE
HARDER, BILLY.
AAH!
YOU JERK!
YOU WERE TRYING
TO KILL GRANDPA!
I'M TELLING MOM!
DAMNIT,
I WAS SO CLOSE.
FOUR THIRD GRADERS
FROM SOUTH PARK, COLORADO
WERE FOUND TRYING
TO VICIOUSLY MURDER
AN INNOCENT
GRANDFATHER.
BOYS, HOW DID YOU GET DRIVEN
SO FAR TO THE EDGE?
WHAT CHANGED YOU INTO SUCH
DEMONIC LITTLE BASTARDS?
WE DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT WE WERE DOING.
WE WERE JUST SITTING THERE
WATCHING "TERRANCE AND PHILLIP".
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP",
AH-HA!
SO IT IS THAT SHOW
THAT IS TO BLAME.
THESE BOYS MINDS
HAVE BEEN TAINTED
BY THE GARBAGE ON TELEVISION
THAT THEY SEE
AND WE ARE FED UP!
OH, GOD,
OH, GOD!
WE HAVE TO STOP THIS SMUT
FROM GOING ON THE AIR!
WE WILL MARCH TO
THE NETWORK AND PROTEST
UNTIL OUR DEMANDS
ARE MET.
NEW YORK,
HERE WE COME!
( loud diarrhea )
WE ARE SPREADING THE WORD
TO THIS ESTABLISHMENT
THAT WE DEMAND
BETTER TELEVISION
FOR OUR CHILDREN!
WE WANT MORE
QUALITY TELEVISION
LIKE "FULL HOUSE"!
I THINK YOU GAVE ME
THE STOMACH FLU, MR. GARRISON.
IT WAS THAT LITTLE KENNY BASTARD
THAT GAVE IT TO ME.
WHOA, MAYOR, YOU MAKING
GRAVY IN THERE?
I JUST HAD
A BROWN BABY BOY.
( laughing )
DUDE, THIS IS SWEET
NOT HAVING PARENTS AROUND.
YEAH, I HOPE THEY PROTEST
TV SHOWS FOREVER.
WHOOPIE!
C'MERE BILLY, I WANNA
SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
DO I
HAVE TO?
YES, YOU DO,
YOU LITTLE PECKER!
I REALIZE THAT THE REASON
YOU WON'T KILL ME
IS BECAUSE YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW I FEEL BILLY.
BUT NOW I FOUND A WAY
TO SHOW YOU
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
TO BE A GRANDPA.
HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE THEY
DOING IN THERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO BE AS OLD AS ME.
ARE YOU READY,
BILLY?
I GUESS.
( Enya's "Sail Away" playing )
OKAY YOU CAN
LET ME OUT NOW.
NOT JUST YET.
LET ME OUT
GRANDPA!
I CAN'T
TAKE IT ANYMORE!
THIS MUSIC
IS TERRIBLE!
IT'S CHEESY,
BUT LAME
AND EERILY SOOTHING
AT THE SAME TIME!
THAT'S IT!
NOW YOU KNOW WHAT IT
FEELS LIKE TO BE A GRANDPA!
GRANDPA I HAD NO IDEA
HOW BAD IT WAS FOR YOU.
NOW I UNDERSTAND.
SO NOW WILL YOU
KILL ME BILLY?
SURE I WILL
GRANDPA.
I WILL.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
OUR PROTEST IS WORKING.
IT'LL WORK,
IT HAS TO.
( man )
LOOK, IT'S THE PRESIDENT
OF THE NETWORK.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
MY NAME IS JOHN WORSON.
I'VE PREPARED A STATEMENT FOR
YOU ON BEHALF OF THE NETWORK.
( clearing throat )
@#$$! YOU.
THANK YOU
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
IF THERE ARE ANY QUESTIONS
YOU MAY DIRECT THEM
TO THAT BRICK WALL
OVER THERE.
HEY, YOU WILL NOT
GET AWAY WITH THIS!
( crowd gasping )
THAT DOES IT!
NO MORE
MR. NICE PROTESTERS!
IT'S TIME
FOR PLAN B.
CAROL, WHERE ARE
THE PORTA-POTTIES?
OVER THERE HON.
WHY, DO YOU NEED TO DROP
SOME FRIENDS OFF AT THE POOL?
OH, YES
INDEEDY.
( laughing )
OKAY, GRANDPA, ALL YOU
HAVE TO DO IS SIT THERE.
WE'LL DO THE REST.
YOU GOT THE COW
ALL TIED UP?
YEP ALL DONE.
OKAY,
C'MON GUYS.
WHY DON'T
WE JUST SHOOT HIM?
YOU DUMB-ASS
CARTMAN.
IT HAS TO LOOK NATURAL
OR ELSE WE'LL GET BUSTED.
YEAH
STUPID.
THAT'S GOOD BILLY,
A LITTLE HIGHER NOW.
THE NETWORK IS NOT
TAKING US SERIOUSLY.
IN THE PAST PEOPLE
HAVE HAD TO DIE
FOR WHAT THEY
BELIEVED IN.
AND WE ARE PREPARED
TO DO THE SAME!
READY?
MR. McCORMIC YOU SHALL BE
A MARTYR TO US ALL.
WE WILL NOT LET
THESE CORPORATE HALF-WITS
RUIN OUR
CHILDREN'S MINDS!
LAUNCH!
( gasping )
WE WILL ALL FOLLOW SUIT
ONE BY ONE
IF THAT'S
WHAT IT TAKES!
( moaning in pain )
ARE YOU READY
GRANDPA?
DOES THE POPE
CRAP IN THE WOODS?
( police radio )
CARRY ON.
OKAY
HERE WE GO.
BYE GRANDPA, IT WAS
NICE KNOWING YOU.
CUT THE DAMN ROPE
ALREADY!
WHAT IS THAT?
IT LOOKS
LIKE DEATH!
IT'S ABOUT TIME,
YOU LAZY-ASS
SON OF A WHORE!
C'MON LET'S GO!
WHAT THE--?
HEY, HE'S COMING
TOWARDS US.
( Cartman )
WHY IS DEATH
COMING AFTER US?
( children screaming )
AAH...!
HELP!
RUN, RUN, RUN!
WHAT ARE
WE GONNA DO?
AS THE DAY
PROGRESSES
MORE AND MORE
SOUTH PARK RESIDENTS
CONTINUE TO SLINGSHOT
THEIR BODIES
INTO THE SIDE OF
THE TOON CENTRAL BUILDING.
TOON CENTRAL IS NOW UNDER
INCREDIBLE PRESSURE
TO CANCEL THE SHOW
AND HAS ALREADY LOST OVER
20 PERCENT OF THEIR SPONSORS.
HERE CAROL,
I THINK IT'S YOUR BOY.
OH, THANKS.
WHAT IS IT
STANLEY, HON?
DID YOU
BREAK SOMETHING?
MOM, DEATH IS HERE
AND HE'S TRYING TO
TAKE US AWAY WITH HIM!
STANLEY, YOU NEED
TO LEAVE MOMMY ALONE.
I'M DOING SOMETHING
VERY, VERY IMPORTANT
FOR YOUR LITTLE
WELL BEING THERE.
( Stan )
Yeah but Mom--!
HERE HONEY,
TALK TO YOUR FATHER.
DID YOU TURN
THE HEAT DOWN?
Dad, Death is coming!
KEEP THE THERMOSTAT
UNDER 70.
TAKE CARE OF
YOUR GRANDFATHER.
DAMNIT!
IF PARENTS
SPENT LESS TIME
WORRYING ABOUT WHAT
THEIR KIDS WATCH ON TV
AND MORE TIME WORRYING
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON
IN THEIR KIDS' LIVES
THIS WORLD WOULD BE
A MUCH BETTER PLACE.
YEAH I THINK THAT PARENTS
ONLY GET SO OFFENDED
BY TELEVISION BECAUSE THEY
RELY ON IT AS A BABY-SITTER
AND THE SOLE EDUCATOR
OF THEIR KIDS.
( mumbling )
TOTALLY DUDE.
AAH!
QUICK, JUMP THROUGH
THE WINDOW!
AAH...!
COME BACK HERE,
YOU SON OF A PANSY!
DON'T LET HIM
TOUCH YOU.
YOU DIE IF
HE TOUCHES YOU!
COME OVER HERE,
YOU SON OF A WHORE!
Oh, Terrance.
What color
is the wind?
Hmm, I don't know,
why don't you check?
( farting )
You farted!
( laughing )
Hey Phillip,
you know what my
spacesuit smells like?
No Terrance,
why don't you tell me?
Well, it smells like
a dirty fart.
( laughing )
HEY LOOK!
Oh, there's one!
( laughing )
HOURS HAVE PAST
AND STILL THE DIE-HARD
SOUTH PARK PARENTS
ARE KILLING THEMSELVES IN FRONT
OF THE TOON CENTRAL BUILDING
ONE BY ONE.
WORSE YET,
THE STOMACH FLU THAT SEEMS TO BE
GOING AROUND IS...
WAIT, WAIT,
I'M GETTING WORD THAT
THE PRESIDENT OF THE NETWORK
IS GOING TO MAKE
A STATEMENT.
WAIT, WAIT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
YOUR NAZI-ASS TACTICS
OF TRYING TO STINK US OUT
WITH YOUR RANCID FECES...
HAS WORKED.
THEREFORE TODAY WE WILL
OFFICIALLY BE TAKING
"TERRANCE AND PHILLIP"
OFF THE NETWORK
AND REPLACING IT WITH RERUNS OF
"SHE'S THE SHERIFF",
STARRING
SUZANNNE SOMERS.
( applause )
GET AWAY FROM HERE AND
TAKE YOUR DIARRHEA WITH YOU!
NOW AT LAST WE CAN
RETURN TO NORMALITY.
Hey, Phillip.
Yes, Terrance?
Is there a penny
stuck in my butt?
I don't know, Terrance,
let me check.
UH-OH, DON'T LOOK PHILLIP,
YOU'RE GONNA GET FARTED ON.
We interrupt this program
to bring you loud static.
( groaning )
AAH!
OH, MY GOD,
THEY KILLED KENNY!
YOU BASTARD!
I GUESS DEATH WAS COMING
AFTER KENNY THE WHOLE TIME.
HEY, YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO KILL ME!
THAT'S NOT FAIR,
GODDAMNIT!
MY GRANDPA ASKED ME
TO KILL HIM AND I DID IT!
WHOA!
BILLY...
GRANDPA?
THAT'S RIGHT
BILLY.
MY NAME'S NOT
BILLY, GRANDPA.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,
WHY DO YOU LOOK ALL HAGGARD?
I ASKED YOU
TO KILL ME, BILLY.
BUT I WAS WRONG,
AND NOW I'M FORCED TO
SPEND ETERNITY IN LIMBO.
"LIMBO"?
I WAS WRONG TO PUT YOU
IN THAT POSITION.
JUST LIKE YOU'RE WRONG TO PUT
LITTLE BILLY IN IT NOW.
YOU'RE SO OBSESSED
WITH ENDING YOUR LIFE
YOU'RE NOT THINKING ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE DOING TO HIS.
YOU MUST WAIT TO DIE
OF NATURAL CAUSES.
BUT I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR 25 YEARS!
LET NATURE RUN ITS COURSE
OR ELSE END UP IN LIMBO!
NATURAL CAUSES, BILLY.
NATURAL CAUSES...
C'MON YOU GUYS,
LET'S GO HOME.
HERE THEY ARE.
WELL,
WE DID IT SON.
WE FOUGHT A BATTLE FOR
YOUR WELL-BEING AND WON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WE GOT "TERRANCE AND PHILLIP"
TAKEN OFF THE AIR.
YOU SON-OF-A-BITCH,
YOUR MOM SUCKS!
BUT LOOK
WHAT THEY PUT ON.
And now back to
"She's the Sheriff".
NO!
GOD, NO!
You were the one behind
all the shenanigans.
Yeah well you're the
stupid 'ho that started it.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
Up yours,
butt-munch!
WH-WH-WHAT?!
C'MON EVERYBODY,
BACK TO NEW YORK!
NOW THAT "TERRANCE AND PHILLIP"
HAS BEEN TAKEN OFF THE AIR,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
FOR ENTERTAINMENT?
I DON'T KNOW, WE CAN START
BREATHING GAS FUMES.
MY UNCLE SAYS THAT
SMOKING CRACK IS KINDA COOL.
WHY DON'T WE WATCH SOME OF
THOSE PORNO MOVIE THINGIES?
COOL!
YEAH!
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING GRANDPA?
I'M PLANNING
A TRIP TO AFRICA.
DID YOU KNOW OVER 400 PEOPLE
ARE EATEN NATURALLY
BY LIONS IN AFRICA
EVERY YEAR?
THAT'S MY
SILLY GRANDPA.
( laughing )